{
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "category": "Character",
            "question": "Who is Lancelot's sister?",
            "correct_answer": "Guinevere",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Karina",
                "Selena",
                "Layla"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "category": "Character",
            "question": "Who is Gusion's brother?",
            "correct_answer": "Aamon",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Lancelot",
                "Chou",
                "Barats"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "category": "Character",
            "question": "Which hero has a monkey friend?",
            "correct_answer": "Claude",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Irithel",
                "Diggie",
                "Alpha"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "category": "Character",
            "question": "Which squad does Rafaela belong?",
            "correct_answer": "S.A.B.E.R",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Lightborn",
                "V.E.N.O.M",
                "She hasn't had a squad"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "category": "Character",
            "question": "What is Leomord's animal friend?",
            "correct_answer": "A horse",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "A tiger",
                "A monkey",
                "An owl"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "category": "Character",
            "question": "What is the first hero in Mobile Legends?",
            "correct_answer": "Miya",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Layla",
                "Tigreal",
                "Eudora"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "category": "Character",
            "question": "Who is Selena's sister?",
            "correct_answer": "Karina",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Fanny",
                "Chang'e",
                "Rafaela"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "category": "Character",
            "question": "Which two heroes are in romantic relationships?",
            "correct_answer": "Lancelot & Odette",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Franco & Fanny",
                "Khufra & Freya",
                "Gusion & Layla"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "category": "Character",
            "question": "Which hero is inspired by Bruce Lee?",
            "correct_answer": "Chou",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Paquito",
                "Gloo",
                "Yu Zhong"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "category": "Character",
            "question": "Along with Zhask and Yve, who is another hero that is an alien?",
            "correct_answer": "Karrie",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Cyclops",
                "Bane",
                "Gord"
            ]
        }
    ]
}